Cultural Survival Records MS180
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Office files, 1919 -- 2013; MS180.004; 46.7 Linear Feet
  - Efe-Luth, 1939 -- 2011; MS180.004.003
    - James Bay Cree/ Hydro Quebec, 1991 -- 2000; MS180.004.027.00012 (Box 27)
    - JMS: Contract Negotiations, 1992; MS180.004.027.00013 (Box 27)
    - JMS-- File, 1991 -- 1994; MS180.004.027.00014 (Box 27)
    - Job Applicants, 2004; MS180.004.027.00015 (Box 27)
    - Kakuma Refugee Library, 1998; MS180.004.027.00016 (Box 27)
    - Kaplan, Hillard: Technology and Food Inquisition Among Two Amazonian Peoples Draft, 1989; MS180.004.027.00017 (Box 27)
    - Karim, Lamia: "Nationalism, Gender, and Human Rights: The State of the Subaltern Adivasi Woman in Bangladesh", 1997; MS180.004.027.00018 (Box 27)
    - Kasiisi, 1999 -- 2005; MS180.004.027.00019 (Box 27)
    - Keck, Mimi, 1986; MS180.004.027.00020 (Box 27)
    - Keleman, P.: The Politics of the Famine in Ethiopia and Eritrea, 1985; MS180.004.027.00021 (Box 27)
    - Keller, E.J.: Ethiopian Socialism and Ag. Dev., 1985; MS180.004.027.00022 (Box 27)
    - Kellog Talk and comments, 1991; MS180.004.027.00023 (Box 27)
    - Kelly, J.: Food Aid and the Emergency Syndrome, 1981; MS180.004.027.00024 (Box 27)
    - Kenya, 1980; MS180.004.027.00025 (Box 27)
    - Ketel, J (Oxfam): Refugee Influx (2): Assessment of the situation in the Damazin/Kurmuk/Yubus areas of the Sudan, 1985; MS180.004.027.00026 (Box 27)
    - Ketto Settlements, 1986; MS180.004.027.00027 (Box 27)
    - Kidane, A.:Famine and Mortality Fertility and Population, 1986; MS180.004.027.00028 (Box 27)
    - Knudsen Packing Copy, 1991; MS180.004.027.00029 (Box 27)
    - Knudsen Promo Info, 1992 -- 1994; MS180.004.027.00030 (Box 27)
    - Koasek Abenaki, 2006; MS180.004.027.00031 (Box 27)
    - Kurdish Program, 1988; MS180.004.027.00032 (Box 27)
    - L. America: "Toward Renewed Econ. Growth in Latin America", 1997; MS180.004.027.00033 (Box 27)
    - L. America: "Toward Renewed Econ. Growth in Latin America"-- Ecuador-- Indigenous Organizations, 1997; MS180.004.027.00034 (Box 27)
    - L. America: "Toward Renewed Econ. Growth in Latin America"-- Firpo, J Net Project, 1997; MS180.004.027.00035 (Box 27)
    - L. America: "Toward Renewed Econ. Growth in Latin America"-- Guatemala, 1997; MS180.004.027.00036 (Box 27)
    - L. America: "Toward Renewed Econ. Growth in Latin America" Hydrovía Info, 1995 -- 1997; MS180.004.027.00037 (Box 27)
    - Lake Natron, 2007; MS180.004.027.00038 (Box 27)
    - Lamphere, Louise-- Symbolic Elements in Navajo Ritual, 1968; MS180.004.027.00039 (Box 27)
    - Language and People's Database, 1990; MS180.004.027.00040 (Box 27)
    - The Language Gathering, 2009; MS180.004.027.00041 (Box 27)
    - La Rocco Associates, 1991; MS180.004.027.00042 (Box 27)
    - Larry, 2002 -- 2003; MS180.004.027.00043 (Box 27)
    - Lat. Am. Comm. Laws, 2007; MS180.004.027.00044 (Box 27)
    - Latin Amer Regional Reports, 1997; MS180.004.027.00045 (Box 27)
    - Laurel Hill Inc, 1995; MS180.004.027.00046 (Box 27)
    - Law Initiative, 2000; MS180.004.027.00047 (Box 27)
    - Legal Representation on Agreements: Cooley and Arrison and Olden, 2007; MS180.004.027.00048 (Box 27)
    - Legal Services Contract w/ Cooley/Goodward, 2007; MS180.004.027.00049 (Box 27)
    - Lerner, Paula, 1998; MS180.004.027.00050 (Box 27)
    - Letters and Project Proposals/Abstracts, 1998 -- 2004; MS180.004.027.00051 (Box 27)
    - Liberia: War, Human Rights, and Refugees, 1990 -- 1991; MS180.004.027.00052 (Box 27)
    - Library (CS), 2003 -- 2004; MS180.004.027.00053 (Box 27)
    - Library, 1998 -- 2000; MS180.004.027.00054 (Box 27)
    - Libre Determinación: Niños y Jóvenes y Indígenas, 2003; MS180.004.027.00055 (Box 27)
    - Lists, 2006 -- 2008; MS180.004.027.00056 (Box 27)
    - Local Action Global Impact, 2005; MS180.004.027.00057 (Box 27)
    - Local Events Blackbird Café, 1994; MS180.004.027.00058 (Box 27)
    - Local Events - Cambridge Expo, 1994; MS180.004.028.00001 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - Cambridge River Fest, 1994; MS180.004.028.00002 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - Film, Food & the Future, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.004.028.00003 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - General Notes, 1994 -- 1995; MS180.004.028.00004 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - Music - Bands, 1994; MS180.004.028.00005 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - Window Display Cambridge Trust, 1995; MS180.004.028.00006 (Box 28)
    - Local Events - World's Fair Central Square, 1994; MS180.004.028.00007 (Box 28)
    - London, Jonathan K.: Amazônia in the American Mind: An Analysis of the U.S. Rainforest Movement, Honors Thesis, 1991; MS180.004.028.00008 (Box 28)
    - Long Range Planning Process, 2010; MS180.004.028.00009 (Box 28)
    - Loose Ends - Staff Meeting Notes and Correspondence, 2002 -- 2003; MS180.004.028.00010 (Box 28)
    - Lutheran Assistance, 1980 -- 1983; MS180.004.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - Ellen Lutz, 2002 -- 2010; MS180.004.004
    - AAA-HR Committee Talks, 2008; MS180.004.028.00012 (Box 28)
    - AAA HR Panel, 2007; MS180.004.028.00013 (Box 28)
    - Anchorage Declaration, 2009; MS180.004.028.00014 (Box 28)
    - Assorted Loose Materials, 2004 -- 2010; MS180.004.028.00015 (Box 28)
    - Auction, 2005; MS180.004.028.00016 (Box 28)
    - Center for Int'l Envir. Law Annual Report, 2005; MS180.004.028.00017 (Box 28)
    - Chile Mission, 2006; MS180.004.028.00018 (Box 28)
    - Clavero, Indigenous Rights to Participation, 2005; MS180.004.028.00019 (Box 28)
    - Climate Change, 2009; MS180.004.028.00020 (Box 28)
    - Contacts - Ecuador, 2005; MS180.004.028.00021 (Box 28)
    - Contingency Plans if Financial Problems Cont'd, 2008; MS180.004.028.00022 (Box 28)
    - Prep for Copenhagen Climate Meetings, 2009; MS180.004.028.00023 (Box 28)
    - CS Study on HR Reporting on Ips by other HR NGOs, 2005; MS180.004.028.00024 (Box 28)
    - "Deadicated" Concert Proceeds (Bulletproof & Arista), 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.028.00025 (Box 28)
    - Dreamtime Exhibition of Aboriginal Art Catalogue, 2008; MS180.004.028.00026 (Box 28)
    - Earthrights, 2005 -- 2007; MS180.004.028.00027 (Box 28)
    - Ecologic, 2006 -- 2007; MS180.004.028.00028 (Box 28)
    - EL AAA Presentation - Lessons from 20 months at Cultural Survival, 2005; MS180.004.028.00029 (Box 28)
    - EL Application for AAA HR Comm., 2003 -- 2006; MS180.004.028.00030 (Box 28)
    - EL Fundraising Activities - Current, 2010; MS180.004.028.00031 (Box 28)
    - Environmental Foundations, 2008; MS180.004.028.00032 (Box 28)
    - Event Donations, 2005; MS180.004.028.00033 (Box 28)
    - Forest People's Program, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.028.00034 (Box 28)
    - Foundation Possibilities, 2004; MS180.004.028.00035 (Box 28)
    - Fred Jones Fraud Scam, 2004; MS180.004.028.00036 (Box 28)
    - Fund Raising Planning, 2010; MS180.004.028.00037 (Box 28)
    - Fundraising - Foundations - Current, 2007 -- 2008; MS180.004.028.00038 (Box 28)
    - Fundraising Meeting Notes, 2004; MS180.004.028.00039 (Box 28)
    - Fundraising Plan, 2005; MS180.004.028.00040 (Box 28)
    - Fundraising Skills, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.028.00041 (Box 28)
    - Genographics, 2006; MS180.004.028.00042 (Box 28)
    - Gold Mining, 2006; MS180.004.028.00043 (Box 28)
    - Huaorani Case - Ecuador, 2003 -- 2005; MS180.004.028.00044 (Box 28)
    - Huichol, 2005; MS180.004.028.00045 (Box 28)
    - Indian Boarding School Lawsuits / Reparations - US, 2008; MS180.004.028.00046 (Box 28)
    - Indian Law Resource Center Donor List, 2005; MS180.004.028.00047 (Box 28)
    - "Indigenous Organizations" OUP HR Encyclopedia, 2008; MS180.004.028.00048 (Box 28)
    - Investments, 2004; MS180.004.028.00049 (Box 28)
    - IPs in Ecuador, 2004 -- 2005; MS180.004.028.00050 (Box 28)
    - IPs & Politics Donna Lee Van Cott Talk, 2006; MS180.004.028.00051 (Box 28)
    - IPs & Water Rights, 2002 -- 2006; MS180.004.028.00052 (Box 28)
    - Maasai, 2006; MS180.004.028.00053 (Box 28)
    - Macdonald, Indigenous Rights in Latin America for Minority Rights Guide, 2005; MS180.004.028.00054 (Box 28)
    - Mapuche, 2005; MS180.004.029.00001 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Marketing & Messaging Lyn Chamberlin Phases 1 & 2, 2008; MS180.004.029.00002 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Martha Clare Evert, 2008; MS180.004.029.00003 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Memo on Mtg. w/James Cameron, 2010; MS180.004.029.00004 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Mexico - Indigenous Radio, 2005; MS180.004.029.00005 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Mexico Trip, 2004; MS180.004.029.00006 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Minority Rights Group, 2005; MS180.004.029.00007 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - National Geographic Genographic Project, 2005; MS180.004.029.00008 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Native American, 2010; MS180.004.029.00009 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Navajo Nation vs US Forest Serv., 2006; MS180.004.029.00010 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Northern Arapaho Tribe, 2010; MS180.004.029.00011 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Oxfam USA, 2005; MS180.004.029.00012 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Pia Party, 2005; MS180.004.029.00013 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - CS Program Council Mtg., 2005; MS180.004.029.00014 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Projects w. Harv. HR Law Clinic, 2006; MS180.004.029.00015 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Radio PCI Freeplay..., 2005; MS180.004.029.00016 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - REPORT CARD Harvard Student Papers Spring, 2007; MS180.004.029.00017 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - RFK - Dutia da Costa Amicus (Brazil Curiae Brif, 2004; MS180.004.029.00018 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Right to Health Ariel Spreying in Ecuador, 2007; MS180.004.029.00019 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Right to Health of IPS, 2007; MS180.004.029.00020 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Rights Action, 2003; MS180.004.029.00021 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Ringing Rocks, MS180.004.029.00022 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Romeo Saganash Paper Review for Oxford Amnesty Book, 2005; MS180.004.029.00023 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Sacred Land Film Project, 2006; MS180.004.029.00024 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Salsaca, Ecuador, 2005; MS180.004.029.00025 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - SAN, 2005; MS180.004.029.00026 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Sarayaku Case, 2004; MS180.004.029.00027 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Society for Threatened Peoples GFBV (Germany), 2005; MS180.004.029.00028 (Box data_value_missing_70ba2b695041d9aaeb83dd975c9981ea)
    - Special Event Venues, 2005; MS180.004.029.00029 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Survival Int'l, 2003; MS180.004.029.00030 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Technology Committee, 2005; MS180.004.029.00031 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Tiverton Bazaar, 2003; MS180.004.029.00032 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Tom Bird, 2010; MS180.004.029.00033 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Travel Brochure, 2005; MS180.004.029.00034 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Uranium Mining on US IP Lands, 2009; MS180.004.029.00035 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Washington Contacts, 2005; MS180.004.029.00036 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Weekly Giving Reports, 2005; MS180.004.029.00037 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Western MA, 2005; MS180.004.029.00038 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Western Shoshone Case, 2002; MS180.004.029.00039 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Winona LaDuke Event, 2006; MS180.004.029.00040 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Winter Bazaar Analysis Feedback, 2005; MS180.004.029.00041 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
  - Lyo-TAFT, 1919 -- 2013; MS180.004.005
    - Lyon, A.: Torture and the Violation of Human Rights in Tigray, Eth., 1986; MS180.004.029.00042 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Maasai, 1996; MS180.004.029.00043 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Maasai Correspondence, 1995; MS180.004.029.00044 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Maasai Finances, 1996; MS180.004.029.00045 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Maasai Updates/Photos, 1995; MS180.004.029.00046 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - MacDonald, Ted: Correspondence, 1985; MS180.004.029.00047 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - MacDonald, Ted: Papers, 1992; MS180.004.029.00048 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - MacDonald, Ted: Trip Reports, 1985; MS180.004.029.00049 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - MacPherson, Sonia: "A Blueprint for Survival: Khetsun Sangpo Tibetan Village", 2001; MS180.004.029.00050 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Madre de Dios, Peru Alto Purus, 2006; MS180.004.029.00051 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Malawi, 1993; MS180.004.029.00052 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Mali: Drought + Famine, 1985; MS180.004.029.00053 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Mali: KOMO, 1984; MS180.004.029.00054 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Manipur Struggle Project, 2003; MS180.004.029.00055 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Manz, Beatriz: Repatriation and Reintegration: An Arduous Process in Guatemala Draft, 1987; MS180.004.029.00056 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Maps, 1987; MS180.004.029.00057 (Box data_value_missing_920f845f8b6ba781d27a077fc44c5e88)
    - Marion Foundation, 2001; MS180.004.030.00001 (Box 30)
    - Market Assessment Program: CSE, 1994; MS180.004.030.00002 (Box 30)
    - Marketing Cultural Survival, 2007 -- 2008; MS180.004.030.00003 (Box 30)
    - Masai, 1988 -- 1999; MS180.004.030.00004 (Box 30)
    - Masai Education LADAMA, 2003; MS180.004.030.00005 (Box 30)
    - Masai Jewelry Project Application, 2003; MS180.004.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Masai Oral History Request for Funding, 2003; MS180.004.030.00007 (Box 30)
    - Masai Video Project Proposal & Application, 2003; MS180.004.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - Masks Rituals, 1960 -- 1989; MS180.004.030.00009 (Box 30)
    - Maya, 1981 -- 1994; MS180.004.030.00010 (Box 30)
    - Maya Manche Contract, 1992; MS180.004.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - Maya Manche (Kekchi) Correspondence, 1991 -- 2001; MS180.004.030.00012 (Box 30)
    - Maya Manche (Kekchi) Donation Info, 1994 -- 1998; MS180.004.030.00013 (Box 30)
    - Maya Manche (Kekchi) Financial Statements, 1992 -- 1997; MS180.004.030.00014 (Box 30)
    - Maya Manche (Kekchi) Project Reports, 1992 -- 1998; MS180.004.030.00015 (Box 30)
    - Mayans, 1984 -- 2013; MS180.004.030.00016 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, Biorn: Current Leaders Publishing, 1989 -- 1990; MS180.004.030.00017 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, Biorn: Research Proposal, "The Growth and Transformation of Brazilian Rural Workers Unions, 1964-1985", 1986; MS180.004.030.00018 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, David: Correspondence, Paul Minnis, 1984; MS180.004.030.00019 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, David: Correspondence Regarding MacArthur Foundation, 1988; MS180.004.030.00020 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, David: Correspondence, West/Pachter, 1999; MS180.004.030.00021 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, David: In Defense of Culture, 1984; MS180.004.030.00022 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, David: Living in Leviathan, 1984; MS180.004.030.00023 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, Pia: Correspondence, 2001 -- 2004; MS180.004.030.00024 (Box 30)
    - Maybury-Lewis, Pia: Exchange Report Survey, 1980; MS180.004.030.00025 (Box 30)
    - McCann, J.: Social Impact of Drought in Africa, 1985; MS180.004.030.00026 (Box 30)
    - McGovern Hearings, 2010; MS180.004.030.00027 (Box 30)
    - McGovern, James - Ecuador, 2008; MS180.004.030.00028 (Box 30)
    - Mead, Margaret: Correspondence and News Clippings, 1975 -- 1977; MS180.004.030.00029 (Box 30)
    - Membership, 1996 -- 2002; MS180.004.030.00030 (Box 30)
    - Membership: Lapsed Member Survey, 1998; MS180.004.030.00031 (Box 30)
    - Membership: Member Revamp, 2001 -- 2002; MS180.004.030.00032 (Box 30)
    - Membership: Premiums, 1997; MS180.004.030.00033 (Box 30)
    - Membership: Promoting Membership, 1999; MS180.004.030.00034 (Box 30)
    - Membership Report, 2001; MS180.004.030.00035 (Box 30)
    - Mennonite Central Committee - Canada, 1984 -- 1986; MS180.004.030.00036 (Box 30)
    - Mex Gov't - EZLN Proposed Accord, 1994 -- 1996; MS180.004.030.00037 (Box 30)
    - Mexico, 1983 -- 1996; MS180.004.030.00038 (Box 30)
    - México: ANPIBAC - "Los Grupos Etnicos de México y el Estado Mexicano" Summary, 1983; MS180.004.030.00039 (Box 30)
    - Mexico: Development, 1988 -- 1994; MS180.004.030.00040 (Box 30)
    - Mexico Indians, 2002; MS180.004.030.00041 (Box 30)
    - Miller, Christopher: "Natural History, Economic Botany, and Germplasm Conversation of the Brazil Nut Tree" Thesis, 1990; MS180.004.030.00042 (Box 30)
    - Miller and Wood, Anthropology: The Study of Humanity - Royalties Contract, 1999 -- 2005; MS180.004.030.00043 (Box 30)
    - Mindinao / Taft / Eileen Moore Quinn, 2006; MS180.004.030.00044 (Box 30)
    - Mining and Indigenous Peoples, 1996 -- 2003; MS180.004.030.00045 (Box 30)
    - Mining in Guatemala, 2006; MS180.004.030.00046 (Box 30)
    - Minorities - Centro di Documentazione Sulle Minoranze Etniche, MS180.004.030.00047 (Box 30)
    - Minority/Indigenous Issues HR - Encuentro, 1993; MS180.004.030.00048 (Box 30)
    - Mission Statement Info, 1997; MS180.004.030.00049 (Box 30)
    - MIT Event: Human Rights in Melody & Image, 2004; MS180.004.030.00050 (Box 30)
    - Mitchell, J.J., WFP Wollo: Situation Report, 1985; MS180.004.030.00051 (Box 30)
    - CS Mktg Clips / Xeroxes, 1989; MS180.004.030.00052 (Box 30)
    - Mohawk Borders Trip - Newsletters, 2000 -- 2006; MS180.004.030.00053 (Box 30)
    - Mohawk Borders Trip - Notes, 2006; MS180.004.030.00054 (Box 30)
    - Mohegan Sun Information, 2004; MS180.004.030.00055 (Box 30)
    - Moller, Jonathan, 2002; MS180.004.030.00056 (Box 30)
    - Mon Relief and Development Committee Monthly Reports, 2005; MS180.004.030.00057 (Box 30)
    - Monday Developments, 1990; MS180.004.030.00058 (Box 30)
    - Moneta, Jonathan: Africa- Epupa Dam Himba Indigenous, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.004.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Monograph Series (CS) [1 of 2], 1995 -- 2000; MS180.004.031.00002 (Box 31)
    - Monograph Series (CS) [2 of 2], 1993 -- 1997; MS180.004.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Morgan Stanley Documents, 2007; MS180.004.031.00004 (Box 31)
    - Morocco, 1981 -- 2004; MS180.004.031.00005 (Box 31)
    - Morocco: US-Morocco| Morocco: Foreign Relations, 1981 -- 1987; MS180.004.031.00006 (Box 31)
    - Moskitu Indians: Booklets and Long Articles, 1984 -- 1986; MS180.004.031.00007 (Box 31)
    - Moskitu Indians: Magazine Articles, 1981 -- 1987; MS180.004.031.00008 (Box 31)
    - Moskitu Indians: Newsletters and Correspondence, 1980 -- 1986; MS180.004.031.00009 (Box 31)
    - Mountain Voices, 2002; MS180.004.031.00010 (Box 31)
    - Mozambique: Refugees, 1986 -- 1995; MS180.004.031.00011 (Box 31)
    - Multi-lateral Development Banks, 1984 -- 1985; MS180.004.031.00012 (Box 31)
    - Museum of Science Event, May 10, 1992, MS180.004.031.00013 (Box 31)
    - Myrna Cunningham Case, 1982; MS180.004.031.00014 (Box 31)
    - NA Gaming, 1993 -- 1996; MS180.004.031.00015 (Box 31)
    - NA General, 1991 -- 1993; MS180.004.031.00016 (Box 31)
    - NA Resources and Rights, 1993 -- 1996; MS180.004.031.00017 (Box 31)
    - NA Soverignty, 1988 -- 1996; MS180.004.031.00018 (Box 31)
    - NA Stereotypes, 1980 -- 1995; MS180.004.031.00019 (Box 31)
    - Naga Peoples Movement for Human Rights, 2006; MS180.004.031.00020 (Box 31)
    - Namibia Development Briefing, 1991 -- 1994; MS180.004.031.00021 (Box 31)
    - Namibia Indigenous Peoples San Bushmen, 1984 -- 1993; MS180.004.031.00022 (Box 31)
    - Namibia Publications, 1980 -- 1991; MS180.004.031.00023 (Box 31)
    - Narhada Bachao Andola (NBA) The Narmada Movement, 1995 -- 1999; MS180.004.031.00024 (Box 31)
    - Narmada- Activist Voices Letters, 1994 -- 1998; MS180.004.031.00025 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Conference Day: Visuals, 1997 -- 1999; MS180.004.031.00026 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Dam Project, 1999; MS180.004.031.00027 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Resources Emails, 1999; MS180.004.031.00028 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Project-- Articles, 1992; MS180.004.031.00029 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Project-- Background Information, 1992 -- 1999; MS180.004.031.00030 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Recent News, 1999; MS180.004.031.00031 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Recent News|Current News Narmada Valley, 1999; MS180.004.031.00032 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Recent News|Narmada "A Poetic License" by B.G.Verghese, 1999; MS180.004.031.00033 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Recent News|Narmada News Releases, 1999; MS180.004.031.00034 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Research|Erian, Gina|Narmada- Indian Federal Govt, 1991 -- 1999; MS180.004.031.00035 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Speakers List|Speakers/Potential November Conference '99, 1999; MS180.004.031.00036 (Box 31)
    - Narmada Valley|November Conference '99- Multimedia Ideas Video, 1999; MS180.004.031.00037 (Box 31)
    - Nat Geo, 2000 -- 2002; MS180.004.031.00038 (Box 31)
    - Nat Geo Haiti, 2002; MS180.004.031.00039 (Box 31)
    - National Center for First Nations Governance, 2007; MS180.004.031.00040 (Box 31)
    - National Geographic, 2003; MS180.004.031.00041 (Box 31)
    - National Geographic, 2002; MS180.004.031.00042 (Box 31)
    - National Geographic CS, 2000; MS180.004.031.00043 (Box 31)
    - National Geographic 2 Cultural Survival, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.031.00044 (Box 31)
    - National Geographic CS Proposal, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic: CS/NGS, 1999 -- 2003; MS180.004.032.00002 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic CS/NGS Millenium Stories, 1999 -- 2001; MS180.004.032.00003 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic/Cultural Survival, 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.032.00004 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic:Cultural Survival 2001 [1 of 2], 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic:Cultural Survival 2001 [2 of 2], 2000 -- 2001; MS180.004.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic- Cultural Survival Ethnosphere Voodoo Project, 2003; MS180.004.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic: Ethnosphere, 2001 -- 2002; MS180.004.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic Expeditions Council, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.032.00009 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic Genographic Project, 2006; MS180.004.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic N.G. Contracts and Expenses, etc., 2001 -- 2002; MS180.004.032.00011 (Box 32)
    - National Geographic Proposal- Cultural Survival, 1999 -- 2000; MS180.004.032.00012 (Box 32)